<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Slow Man Tofu</title>
    <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Slow Man Tofu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 18:39:47 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.slowmantofu.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall (apart) Tour 2017</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/tour_poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 18:39:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/tour_poster/</guid>
      <description>Sheep on the farm, Howe Island, ON.
And so it begins! In just over a week I&amp;rsquo;m hitting the road to play 10 shows in 11 nights. That&amp;rsquo;s really the longest string of concerts I&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. It fills me with joy and trepidation, excitement and nervousness.
Touring as a sound technician with the Caravan Stage Company came to an end 5 weeks ago and my life is still an adjustment to living on land in a house as opposed to a boat at sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touring Ontario &#43; Québec</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/novembtour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/novembtour/</guid>
      <description>Tonight the Caravan Stage Company performs its last show in Vancouver on False Creek. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun being the Sound Engineer on this tour that wraps up at the end of this month. Nine months living on a boat and travelling the seas has been a long time. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to get back to making music more often, and for a Slow Man Tofu tour this autumn!
Today I&amp;rsquo;m releasing details for 9 tour dates scheduled for late November in Ontario and Montréal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</guid>
      <description>Send an email to inquire about booking Slow Man Tofu: dirty.clothes.records@gmail.com.
Upcoming Performances November 15, 2017 - ELMS and Slow Man Tofu - The Garnet, Peterborough, ON
November 16, 2017 - Slow Man Tofu and Jonathan Davies - House concert, Harrowsmith, ON
November 17, 2017 - Slow Man Tofu - Musiikki Cafe, Kingston, ON
November 18, 2017 - Slow Man Tofu at Night Kitchen Too - Belleville, ON
November 20, 2017 - Del Stephen, Moonfox and Slow Man Tofu - St.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</guid>
      <description>Steer The largest-scope Slow Man Tofu album - Steer - was co-produced by myself and Matt Rogalsky of Memory Device (PS I Love You, The Gertrudes). Guest drummers Andy Love and Arden Rogalsky invaluably lent their skills to the recordings. Special thanks to Katie Beth for backing vocals on two of the tracks and to Jared Mackay for some banjo pickin’.
Steer by Slow Man Tofu Magicmouth Magicmouth is a release of 5 lengthy improvised works for guitar, voice, and midi instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</guid>
      <description>This music video I created for a small side project called &amp;lsquo;Snakes 4 President&amp;rsquo;, released December 2016.
 Here is a music video I made for Ramblings, from the album Steer, released August 2016. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly just some random video clips I had on my camera at the time, applied with some tint filters.
 For David Blackwood by Slow Man Tofu, performed live at La Passe, Montreal, April 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</guid>
      <description>Slow Man Tofu - “Magicmouth”  Magicmouth is the latest release from David Parker&#39;s multi-tentacled creature called Slow Man Tofu. Where his previous tape, Steer, was anchored in rock and folk songwriting with a occasional forays into freer-form experimentation, Magicmouth abandons all conventions of song structure and instead floats on extended and effected guitar improvisations, layered with synthetic tones and dubby, echoey half-singing. David allows his slow paths to wander uninhibited, resulting in an expansive collection of tracks that moves between drone, doom, noisy free improv, and ambient music.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victoria</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/victoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 21:40:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/victoria/</guid>
      <description>I’m living in Victoria, BC for the next month while I’m on vacation from being the Sound Engineer with the Caravan Stage Company. We’ve been touring internationally since April, and it’s been a thrill to work with them. It’s given me time to write new songs, and lots of memories and experiences to write about. I hope to record these in 2018.
The Caravan Stage Company tours on a 90 foot tall ship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 12:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>Fire Moss at Poisson Noir, Montreal. I briefly played in Slow Collapse in the Spring of 2016. Here is our gear set up at a house concert in Montreal. Here I am playing upright bass with Andrew Burrows on the drums at Union Gallery, Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, 2014. Poster design for a live broadcast show on CFRC radio. Trying out new basses in Toronto. A little wearable sensor I created for a contemporary circus performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>David Parker is a multi-instrumental musician, composer, sound designer, digital media artist, and software programmer currently on tour with the Caravan Stage Company.
Music David is a singer-songwriter who performs his songs in a folk-rock act called Slow Man Tofu. He has released 2 albums and performed nearly 2 dozen shows around Ontario and Quebec. For 4 years he played upright bass and electronics as part of the experimental duo Fire Moss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>