<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>David Parker</title>
    <link>https://dparker.ca/</link>
    <description>Recent content on David Parker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:08:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dparker.ca/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:08:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your email:
Your message:
Send </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open to New Possibilities</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/open-to-new-possibilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jun 2022 09:09:02 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/open-to-new-possibilities/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been a time, hasn&amp;rsquo;t it? Things pick up, then things slow down. The whole world goes through something it&amp;rsquo;s never been through before. How has our appreciation of music changed? Are we more respectful of it? Did music help people get through the pandemic in such a way that they have newfound understanding of it&amp;rsquo;s value? Does art play an uplifting role in our lives? Will audiences be more appreciative, enthusiastic, engaged listeners?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Take</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/first-take/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 10:34:54 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/first-take/</guid>
      <description>Hi friends, family, listeners, fans. Thanks for reading this blog post. I&amp;rsquo;m writing today to make some exciting announcements about upcoming projects, share some pictures from my camera reel, and mention a few highlights from the last few busy months.
I guess I&amp;rsquo;ll start by announcing that I&amp;rsquo;m no longer going by the name Slow Man Tofu. My solo work and band-leading work will now just be released under my name David Parker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 12:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/music/</guid>
      <description>Every Day Life, 2022 Every Day Life is a short album of spontaneous improvisations I made at Port William Sound studio. Two of the tracks feature duets with Jonas Bonnetta, who also engineered the recordings. It features some field recording contributions from longtime collaborator J. Sinibaldi.
every day life by David Parker Trembling Aspen, 2021 A series of solo improvisations for classical guitar and upright bass. Recorded in September 2019 and March 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Creativity in the Pandemic</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/pandemic-creativity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 10:12:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/pandemic-creativity/</guid>
      <description>Trembling Aspen by David Parker In February I released Trembling Aspen, a series of 9 solo improvisations for the classical guitar and upright bass. It was my second release in the midst of a global pandemic, the first was my full-length album Soft Melody Maker in 2020. Back then I cancelled a small tour and had to put other plans, including rehearsing and performing with a band, on hold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing: Soft Melody Maker</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/soft-melody-maker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2020 16:15:25 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/soft-melody-maker/</guid>
      <description>Soft Melody Maker by Slow Man Tofu A month ago I released Soft Melody Maker, my second full-length release that I co-produced with Matt Rogalsky. This album was created over the course of 4 years from 2016 to 2020. My life had a unique trajectory during this time. Starting out in Kingston, moving to Montreal for half a year, back to Kingston to perform a circus show for two months, off to Halifax for half a year, then to the Caravan Stage Company for a 9-month tour in the US and Canada, then to a small farm on Howe Island, and finally back to Kingston.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2019: The Year of Eska</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/2019-the-year-of-eska/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 11:00:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/2019-the-year-of-eska/</guid>
      <description>A new year has begun and I think I&amp;rsquo;m ready to finally sit back and write some thoughts about my journey through the last year and what it has brought me.
The last two years were special because of the 12CAT Arts Collective. I was a member of the collective and helped put on some of the 4 dozen shows we held in the warmer months when it was nice outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diary Tape</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/diary_tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:07:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/diary_tape/</guid>
      <description>Diary Tape by Slow Man Tofu In 2018 I experienced some upheaval that lead to intense emotions. At the same time I was processing recent life events from 2016 and 2017 that had thrown my daily life upside down. I moved several times, traveled and gave up many of my material possessions. 2018 was overwhelming for me, especially early on, but there were moments of light and lucidity.
The idea for this tape came out of some recording sessions with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dance Flower</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/dance-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 09:35:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/dance-flower/</guid>
      <description>In February 2018 I started jamming with artist, musician, creator, farmer and all-around friend Bree Rappaport. Our first performance in May used an overhead projector with illustrated acetates as a visual space in which to perform an improvised set of music with clarinet, upright bass, voice and digital signal processing.
After that we created a set of demo recordings. We used some recorded interviews on tape cassette, recorded new interviews, then manipulated the tape playback and played clarinet, guitar, banjo, percussion and voice overtop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Light and Laughter Brigade</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/summer_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:04:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/summer_update/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe how long it&amp;rsquo;s been since sitting down to write something on this site. Life has had some major ups and downs in the last 8 months that are impossible to encapsulate in this short message. Instead of trying to say everything, I&amp;rsquo;ll stick to music news.
I was lucky to go to Audiopollination #60 in Toronto at Array Space. It was the 60th edition of the self-curated improvised music series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall (apart) Tour 2017</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/tour_poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 18:39:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/tour_poster/</guid>
      <description>Sheep on the farm, Howe Island, ON.
And so it begins! In just over a week I&amp;rsquo;m hitting the road to play 10 shows in 11 nights. That&amp;rsquo;s the longest string of concerts I&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. It fills me with joy, trepidation, excitement and nervousness.
Touring as a sound technician with the Caravan Stage Company came to an end 5 weeks ago and my life is still an adjustment to living on land in a house as opposed to a boat at sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touring Ontario &#43; Québec</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/novembtour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/novembtour/</guid>
      <description>Tonight the Caravan Stage Company performs its last show in Vancouver on False Creek. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun being the Sound Engineer on this tour that wraps up at the end of the month. Nine months living on a boat and travelling the seas has been a long time. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to get back to making music more often, and for a Slow Man Tofu tour this autumn!
Today I&amp;rsquo;m releasing details for 9 tour dates scheduled for late November in Ontario and Montréal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/shows/</guid>
      <description>Send an email to inquire about booking Slow Man Tofu: david@slowmantofu.com. Upcoming Performances November 21, 2019 - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe + Heart Structure Quartet &amp;amp; Sadaf Amini - Next Church, Kingston
Past Performances April 14, 2019 - Anna Sudac + Slow Man Tofu - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON
April 28, 2019 - Saxsyndrum + Cybersex - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON
May 3, 2019 - Sound of the Mountain, Yumiko Yoshimoto wsg, Local Urchins - 12CAT, Kingston, ON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/video/</guid>
      <description>Live Performance at Synapse Circus Sundays, Tranzac, Toronto - May 2022
Meat Birds music video! Shot on location at Something Else Records, Kingston, ON. Direction: David Parker and Sian Alcorn. Camera: Sian Alcorn and Vince Strohmaier. Special thanks to Matt and Tanya Robinson.
So much to remember - Garden Take is a Dance Flower music video.
Starting Bands by Slow Man Tofu. Produced by Sian Alcorn.
A music video for the improvised guitar jam &amp;lsquo;fragile&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/reviews/</guid>
      <description>David Parker and Linsey Wellman - Live at IMOO, Ottawa 2017 I particularly enjoyed Parker&#39;s bass playing, with his imaginative use of arco techniques and muting to create different sounds, and how he combined the bass with pre-recorded loops. Wellman impressively expanded his repertoire with the baritone (sax), retaining his own style and using the different capabilities of that instrument to create beautiful sounds. And playing together they showed considerable empathy and coordination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victoria</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/posts/victoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 21:40:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/posts/victoria/</guid>
      <description>I’m living in Victoria, BC for the next month while I’m on vacation from being the Sound Engineer with the Caravan Stage Company. We’ve been touring internationally since April, and it’s been a thrill to work with them. It’s given me time to write new songs, and lots of memories and experiences to write about. I hope to record these in 2018.
The Caravan Stage Company tours on a 90 foot tall ship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 12:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>Photo:Sian Alcorn Slow Man Tofu. Photo:Jane Kirby Dance Flower. Cred: Dance Flower 12CAT live karaoke band fundraiser. Cred: Sian Alcorn A still from a video shoot by Sian Alcorn, April 2018. The Light and Laughter Brigade in Niagara Falls. Cred: Del Stephen Del Stephen, Jeff Sinibaldi and David Parker after our CFRC in-studio performance. Cred: Del Stephen Among the CD shelves at CFRC radio. Cred: Del Stephen Fire Moss at Poisson Noir, Montreal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>David Parker is a musician based in Kingston/Katarokwi. David draws on experiences and involvement in community radio as well as computer science to develop an aesthetic that is grounded in community organizing and grassroots music presentation. His influences include cosmic americana, drone, free jazz, folk, and electroacoustic composition. Since the pandemic David has built a recording studio and developed new styles of improvised music for voice, synthesizer, drum machine, harmonica and slide guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
