<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on David Parker</title>
    <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on David Parker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:08:51 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dparker.ca/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 09:08:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your email:
Your message:
Send </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 12:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/music/</guid>
      <description>All of my public music is available on Bandcamp.
Witches&amp;rsquo; Butter, releasing March 2023 In advance of the Witches&amp;rsquo; Butter album release, I dropped the first single, &amp;ldquo;A Murder of Crows at Dawn.&amp;rdquo; Here&amp;rsquo;s a link to the One Sheet.
A Murder of Crows at Dawn by David Parker Every Day Life, 2022 Every Day Life is a short album of spontaneous improvisations I made at Port William Sound studio. Two of the tracks feature duets with Jonas Bonnetta, who also engineered the recordings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/shows/</guid>
      <description>Send an email to inquire about booking Slow Man Tofu: david@slowmantofu.com. Upcoming Performances November 21, 2019 - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe + Heart Structure Quartet &amp;amp; Sadaf Amini - Next Church, Kingston
Past Performances April 14, 2019 - Anna Sudac + Slow Man Tofu - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON
April 28, 2019 - Saxsyndrum + Cybersex - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON
May 3, 2019 - Sound of the Mountain, Yumiko Yoshimoto wsg, Local Urchins - 12CAT, Kingston, ON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/video/</guid>
      <description>Live Performance at Synapse Circus Sundays, Tranzac, Toronto - May 2022
Meat Birds music video! Shot on location at Something Else Records, Kingston, ON. Direction: David Parker and Sian Alcorn. Camera: Sian Alcorn and Vince Strohmaier. Special thanks to Matt and Tanya Robinson.
So much to remember - Garden Take is a Dance Flower music video.
Starting Bands by Slow Man Tofu. Produced by Sian Alcorn.
A music video for the improvised guitar jam &amp;lsquo;fragile&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/reviews/</guid>
      <description>David Parker and Linsey Wellman - Live at IMOO, Ottawa 2017 I particularly enjoyed Parker&#39;s bass playing, with his imaginative use of arco techniques and muting to create different sounds, and how he combined the bass with pre-recorded loops. Wellman impressively expanded his repertoire with the baritone (sax), retaining his own style and using the different capabilities of that instrument to create beautiful sounds. And playing together they showed considerable empathy and coordination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 12:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>Download All Photos
Photo:Sian Alcorn Slow Man Tofu. Photo:Jane Kirby Dance Flower. Cred: Dance Flower 12CAT live karaoke band fundraiser. Cred: Sian Alcorn A still from a video shoot by Sian Alcorn, April 2018. The Light and Laughter Brigade in Niagara Falls. Cred: Del Stephen Del Stephen, Jeff Sinibaldi and David Parker after our CFRC in-studio performance. Cred: Del Stephen Among the CD shelves at CFRC radio. Cred: Del Stephen Fire Moss at Poisson Noir, Montreal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dparker.ca/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dparker.ca/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>David Parker is a musician based in Kingston/Katarokwi. David draws on experiences and involvement in community radio as well as electrical and computer engineering to develop a unique aesthetic that is grounded in community organizing and grassroots music presentation. His influences include cosmic americana, drone, free jazz, folk, and electroacoustic composition. Since the pandemic David has built a recording studio and developed new styles of improvised music for voice, synthesizer, drum machine, harmonica and slide guitar.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
