<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Slow Man Tofu</title>
    <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Slow Man Tofu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</guid>
      <description>Send an email to inquire about booking Slow Man Tofu: dirty.clothes.records@gmail.com.
Past Performances November 25, 2017 - Conz/Jacobs/Preito, Slow Collapse, Egyptian Cotton Arkestra, Del Stephen/Sinibaldi/Parker - 185 Van Horne, Montreal, QC
November 24, 2017 - Slow Man Tofu // Xiao Xuan // Del Stephen - Musical Chairs, Kingston, ON
November 22, 2017 - Spirit of the Inner Child: Spontaneous Collaborations - Array Space, Toronto, ON
November 21, 2017 - Del Stephen // Happy Baby // Slow Man Tofu - The Tranzac Club, Toronto, ON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</guid>
      <description>Steer The largest-scope Slow Man Tofu album - Steer - was co-produced by myself and Matt Rogalsky of Memory Device (PS I Love You, The Gertrudes). Guest drummers Andy Love and Arden Rogalsky invaluably lent their skills to the recordings. Special thanks to Katie Beth for backing vocals on two of the tracks and to Jared Mackay for some banjo pickin’.
Steer by Slow Man Tofu Magicmouth Magicmouth is a release of 5 lengthy improvised works for guitar, voice, and midi instruments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</guid>
      <description>A music video for the improvised guitar jam &amp;lsquo;fragile&amp;rsquo;. Shot in Halifax, NS.
 This music video I created for a small side project called &amp;lsquo;Snakes 4 President&amp;rsquo;, released December 2016.
 Here is a music video I made for Ramblings, from the album Steer, released August 2016. It&amp;rsquo;s mostly just some random video clips I had on my camera at the time, applied with some tint filters.
 For David Blackwood by Slow Man Tofu, performed live at La Passe, Montreal, April 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</guid>
      <description>David Parker and Linsey Wellman - Live at IMOO, Ottawa 2017  I particularly enjoyed Parker&#39;s bass playing, with his imaginative use of arco techniques and muting to create different sounds, and how he combined the bass with pre-recorded loops. Wellman impressively expanded his repertoire with the baritone (sax), retaining his own style and using the different capabilities of that instrument to create beautiful sounds. And playing together they showed considerable empathy and coordination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 12:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>Fire Moss at Poisson Noir, Montreal. I briefly played in Slow Collapse in the Spring of 2016. Here is our gear set up at a house concert in Montreal. Here I am playing upright bass with Andrew Burrows on the drums at Union Gallery, Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, 2014. Poster design for a live broadcast show on CFRC radio. Trying out new basses in Toronto. A little wearable sensor I created for a contemporary circus performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>David Parker is a multi-instrumental musician, composer, sound designer, digital media artist, and software programmer.
Music David is a singer-songwriter who performs his songs in a folk-rock act called Slow Man Tofu. He has released 2 albums, 1 EP, 2 demos and performed over 2 dozen shows around Ontario and Quebec. For 4 years he played upright bass and electronics as part of the experimental duo Fire Moss. Fire Moss released 3 albums, performed at the Tone Deaf Festival, the In The Soil Arts Festival, and was featured on the compilation The Artel Sessions (Otoacoustic).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>