<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on David Parker</title>
    <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on David Parker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 12:03:58 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://slowmantofu.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2021 12:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</guid>
      <description>Trembling Aspen A series of solo improvisations for classical guitar and upright bass. Recorded in September 2019 and March 2020. Released on February 5th 2021.
Trembling Aspen by Slow Man Tofu Soft Melody Maker &amp;ldquo;Slow Man Tofu’s ​Soft Melody Maker​ is, in its themes and some of its presentation, innately familiar and soothing, it is also conversely, in its myriad idiosyncrasies, uniquely disconcerting. What the world needs now is work which transcends binary emotional posturing; which, antithetical to contemporary algorithmic production, doesn’t rely on the psychic conventions of genre, and which stands, lyrically as well as musically, both stoic and delighted, warm and cryptic, subjective yet rational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</guid>
      <description>Send an email to inquire about booking Slow Man Tofu: david@slowmantofu.com. Upcoming Performances November 21, 2019 - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe + Heart Structure Quartet &amp;amp; Sadaf Amini - Next Church, Kingston
Past Performances April 14, 2019 - Anna Sudac + Slow Man Tofu - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON
April 28, 2019 - Saxsyndrum + Cybersex - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON
May 3, 2019 - Sound of the Mountain, Yumiko Yoshimoto wsg, Local Urchins - 12CAT, Kingston, ON</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</guid>
      <description>Meat Birds music video! Shot on location at Something Else Records, Kingston, ON. Direction: David Parker and Sian Alcorn. Camera: Sian Alcorn and Vince Strohmaier. Special thanks to Matt and Tanya Robinson.
 So much to remember - Garden Take is a Dance Flower music video.
 Starting Bands by Slow Man Tofu. Produced by Sian Alcorn.
 A music video for the improvised guitar jam &amp;lsquo;fragile&amp;rsquo;. Shot in Halifax, NS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</guid>
      <description>David Parker and Linsey Wellman - Live at IMOO, Ottawa 2017  I particularly enjoyed Parker&#39;s bass playing, with his imaginative use of arco techniques and muting to create different sounds, and how he combined the bass with pre-recorded loops. Wellman impressively expanded his repertoire with the baritone (sax), retaining his own style and using the different capabilities of that instrument to create beautiful sounds. And playing together they showed considerable empathy and coordination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 12:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>Photo:Sian Alcorn Slow Man Tofu. Photo:Jane Kirby Dance Flower. Cred: Dance Flower 12CAT live karaoke band fundraiser. Cred: Sian Alcorn A still from a video shoot by Sian Alcorn, April 2018. The Light and Laughter Brigade in Niagara Falls. Cred: Del Stephen Del Stephen, Jeff Sinibaldi and David Parker after our CFRC in-studio performance. Cred: Del Stephen Among the CD shelves at CFRC radio. Cred: Del Stephen Fire Moss at Poisson Noir, Montreal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Slow Man Tofu is the singer-songwriter project of musician David Parker. Parker plays in musical, interdisciplinary projects that are experimental, drone, and improvised, collaborating in ensembles and performing solo improvised work.
Under the name Slow Man Tofu he has released a full-length album with producer Matt Rogalsky and performed dozens of shows around Ontario and Quebec. For 4 years he played upright bass and electronics as part of the experimental duo Fire Moss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
