<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Slow Man Tofu</title>
    <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Slow Man Tofu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Shows</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:04:26 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/shows/</guid>
      <description>Send an email to inquire about booking Slow Man Tofu: david@slowmantofu.com. Upcoming Performances November 21, 2019 - Robert Aiki Aubrey Lowe + Heart Structure Quartet &amp;amp; Sadaf Amini - Next Church, Kingston
Past Performances April 14, 2019 - Anna Sudac + Slow Man Tofu - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON April 28, 2019 - Saxsyndrum + Cybersex - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON May 3, 2019 - Sound of the Mountain, Yumiko Yoshimoto wsg, Local Urchins - 12CAT, Kingston, ON May 4th, 2019 - Homegrown Festival Electroacoustic stage - Kingston, ON March 27, 2019 - 12CAT Live Karaoke Band Fundraiser - The Mansion, Kingston, ON March 7, 2019 - Distortion Sour Release with Dance Flower - Stone City Ales, Kingston, ON January 24, 2019 - Slow Man Tofu &amp; Uncoded - Musiikki Cafe, Kingston, ON January 20, 2019 - Reves Sonores w/ guest David Parker, Dance Flower, Caveman TV - Something Else Records, Kingston, ON December 12, 2018 - Slow Man Tofu at Musiikki Cafe, Kingston, ON November 21, 2018 - Holzkopf, Snakes 4 Presidents - 12CAT, Kingston, ON November 10, 2018 - Slow Man Tofu at Musiikki Cafe, Kingston, ON November 1, 2018 - Boyhood, Slow Man Tofu, Konig - 12CAT, Kingston, ON October 21, 2018 - Heart Structure Quartet, Sharkya/Lima, Kraaijeveld/Caloia, Shelby Cohen - La Plante, Montreal, QC October 20, 2018 - Heart Structure Quartet, Ogoda/Chiarelli, Renders - 12CAT, Kingston, ON October 19, 2018 - ELMS, Tandem Trio, Heart Structure Quartet - Sadleir House, Peterborough, ON October 18, 2018 - Pineapple, Heart Structure Quartet, xLq - Tranzac, Toronto, ON August 30 , 2018 - Deux Trois, Dance Flower, Dayna Pirso - The Brooklyn, Kingston, ON July 3rd, 2018 - Baby Cages and Dorothea Paas with Rappaport/Parker - NGB Studios, Kingston, ON June 16th, 2018 - Silent Systems / Lius Rhutilius / Slow Man Tofu - The Mansion, Kingston, ON June 9th, 2018 - DIRTY CLOTHES Vol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Music</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:03:58 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/music/</guid>
      <description>Diary Tape This recording uses audio diary entries and long-form solo improvisations on upright bass, synths, banjo and drums. I had the idea in mind to fill two sides of a 40 minute tape with two 20 minute long compositions. Here it is in its entirety.
Diary Tape by Slow Man Tofu Steer The largest-scope Slow Man Tofu album - Steer - was co-produced by myself and Matt Rogalsky of Memory Device (PS I Love You, The Gertrudes).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 12:22:02 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/video/</guid>
      <description>So much to remember - Garden Take is a Dance Flower music video.
 Starting Bands by Slow Man Tofu. Produced by Sian Alcorn.
 A music video for the improvised guitar jam &amp;lsquo;fragile&amp;rsquo;. Shot in Halifax, NS.
 This music video I created for a small side project called &amp;lsquo;Snakes 4 President&amp;rsquo;.
 Here is a music video I made for Ramblings, from the album Steer, released August 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviews</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 12:04:13 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/reviews/</guid>
      <description>David Parker and Linsey Wellman - Live at IMOO, Ottawa 2017  I particularly enjoyed Parker&#39;s bass playing, with his imaginative use of arco techniques and muting to create different sounds, and how he combined the bass with pre-recorded loops. Wellman impressively expanded his repertoire with the baritone (sax), retaining his own style and using the different capabilities of that instrument to create beautiful sounds. And playing together they showed considerable empathy and coordination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Photos</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 12:04:07 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/photos/</guid>
      <description>12CAT Arts Collective calendar. Dance Flower. 12CAT live karaoke band fundraiser. A still from a video shoot by Sian Alcorn, April 2018. The Light and Laughter Brigade in Niagara Falls. Del Stephen, Jeff Sinibaldi and David Parker after our CFRC in-studio performance. Among the CD shelves at CFRC radio. Fire Moss at Poisson Noir, Montreal. Here I am playing upright bass with Andrew Burrows on the drums at Union Gallery, Queen&amp;rsquo;s University, 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2017 21:45:30 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/pages/about/</guid>
      <description>Slow Man Tofu is the singer-songwriter project of musician David Parker. Parker plays in musical, interdisciplinary projects that are experimental, drone, and improvised, collaborating in ensembles and performing solo improvised work.
Under the name Slow Man Tofu he has released a full-length album with producer Matt Rogalsky and performed dozens of shows around Ontario and Quebec. For 4 years he played upright bass and electronics as part of the experimental duo Fire Moss.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>