<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Slow Man Tofu</title>
    <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Slow Man Tofu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:04:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Light and Laughter Brigade</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/summer_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:04:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/summer_update/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe how long it&amp;rsquo;s been since sitting down to write something on this site. Life has had some major ups and downs in the last 8 months that are impossible to encapsulate in this short message. Instead of trying to say everything, I&amp;rsquo;ll just stick to music news.
I was lucky to go to Audiopollination #60 in Toronto at Array Space. It was the 60th edition of a self-curated improvised music series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall (apart) Tour 2017</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/tour_poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 18:39:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/tour_poster/</guid>
      <description>Sheep on the farm, Howe Island, ON.
And so it begins! In just over a week I&amp;rsquo;m hitting the road to play 10 shows in 11 nights. That&amp;rsquo;s really the longest string of concerts I&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. It fills me with joy and trepidation, excitement and nervousness.
Touring as a sound technician with the Caravan Stage Company came to an end 5 weeks ago and my life is still an adjustment to living on land in a house as opposed to a boat at sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touring Ontario &#43; Québec</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/novembtour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/novembtour/</guid>
      <description>Tonight the Caravan Stage Company performs its last show in Vancouver on False Creek. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun being the Sound Engineer on this tour that wraps up at the end of this month. Nine months living on a boat and travelling the seas has been a long time. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to get back to making music more often, and for a Slow Man Tofu tour this autumn!
Today I&amp;rsquo;m releasing details for 9 tour dates scheduled for late November in Ontario and Montréal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victoria</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/victoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 21:40:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/victoria/</guid>
      <description>I’m living in Victoria, BC for the next month while I’m on vacation from being the Sound Engineer with the Caravan Stage Company. We’ve been touring internationally since April, and it’s been a thrill to work with them. It’s given me time to write new songs, and lots of memories and experiences to write about. I hope to record these in 2018.
The Caravan Stage Company tours on a 90 foot tall ship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>