<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Slow Man Tofu</title>
    <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Slow Man Tofu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 11:00:19 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>2019: The Year of Eska</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/2019-the-year-of-eska/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2020 11:00:19 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/2019-the-year-of-eska/</guid>
      <description>A new year has begun and I think I&amp;rsquo;m ready to finally sit back and write some thoughts about my journey through the last year and what it has brought me.
The last two years were special because of the 12CAT Arts Collective. I was a member of the collective and helped put on some of the 4 dozen shows we held in the warmer months when it was nice outside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Diary Tape</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/diary_tape/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2019 09:07:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/diary_tape/</guid>
      <description>Diary Tape by Slow Man Tofu In 2018 I experienced some upheaval that lead to intense emotions. At the same time I was processing recent life events from 2016 and 2017 that had thrown my daily life upside down. I moved several times, traveled and gave up many of my material possessions. 2018 was overwhelming for me, especially early on, but there were moments of light and lucidity.
The idea for this tape came out of some recording sessions with friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dance Flower</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/dance-flower/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Nov 2018 09:35:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/dance-flower/</guid>
      <description>In February 2018 I started jamming with artist, musician, creator, farmer and all-around friend Bree Rappaport. Our first performance in May used an overhead projector with illustrated acetates as a visual space in which to perform an improvised set of music with clarinet, upright bass, voice and digital signal processing.
After that we created a set of demo recordings. We used some recorded interviews on tape cassette, recorded new interviews, then manipulated the tape playback and played clarinet, guitar, banjo, percussion and voice overtop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Light and Laughter Brigade</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/summer_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2018 13:04:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/summer_update/</guid>
      <description>I can&amp;rsquo;t believe how long it&amp;rsquo;s been since sitting down to write something on this site. Life has had some major ups and downs in the last 8 months that are impossible to encapsulate in this short message. Instead of trying to say everything, I&amp;rsquo;ll stick to music news.
I was lucky to go to Audiopollination #60 in Toronto at Array Space. It was the 60th edition of the self-curated improvised music series.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall (apart) Tour 2017</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/tour_poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Nov 2017 18:39:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/tour_poster/</guid>
      <description>Sheep on the farm, Howe Island, ON.
And so it begins! In just over a week I&amp;rsquo;m hitting the road to play 10 shows in 11 nights. That&amp;rsquo;s the longest string of concerts I&amp;rsquo;ve ever played. It fills me with joy, trepidation, excitement and nervousness.
Touring as a sound technician with the Caravan Stage Company came to an end 5 weeks ago and my life is still an adjustment to living on land in a house as opposed to a boat at sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Touring Ontario &#43; Québec</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/novembtour/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 12:05:40 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/novembtour/</guid>
      <description>Tonight the Caravan Stage Company performs its last show in Vancouver on False Creek. It&amp;rsquo;s been fun being the Sound Engineer on this tour that wraps up at the end of the month. Nine months living on a boat and travelling the seas has been a long time. I&amp;rsquo;m excited to get back to making music more often, and for a Slow Man Tofu tour this autumn!
Today I&amp;rsquo;m releasing details for 9 tour dates scheduled for late November in Ontario and Montréal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Victoria</title>
      <link>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/victoria/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2017 21:40:52 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.slowmantofu.com/posts/victoria/</guid>
      <description>I’m living in Victoria, BC for the next month while I’m on vacation from being the Sound Engineer with the Caravan Stage Company. We’ve been touring internationally since April, and it’s been a thrill to work with them. It’s given me time to write new songs, and lots of memories and experiences to write about. I hope to record these in 2018.
The Caravan Stage Company tours on a 90 foot tall ship.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>